FROM ME TO YOU
AFTER SCHOOL
- Good morning!
- Oh, hi!
- What's up?
- Oh. Sadako. Morning.
Oh hey, ' Sadako!
Yano... Yoshida... M- ' morning.
It's happening... the moment I've been
dreaming about my entire life... is becoming
reality. This is the best!
What's with ' that face?
If I don't keep on frowning like
this, I'm pretty sure I'll cry.
If you do that, people are
gonna think you're angry, ' y'know?
If you're happy, smile!
- Uh... Never mind, you don't have to.
- That's somehow worse.
You definitely have a gloomy
vibe to you no matter what, so...
At this point, why don't you think about
just using that image to your advantage?
But what do you mean by that?
Huh?
Hey! You made it!
Kazehaya...
He's so nice.
Uh...
- Morning.
- You too, Ryu.
- Hm?
Ah... Right~ morning.
Oh... Uh~ g-g-good morning.
- He's nice too.
- Wait, who were you again?
Come on, Ryu, get it together.
At least remember your classmates.
It's okay, I don't really stand out so...!
-: Well, not in a good way]
- My name's Sawako
- Kuronuma. Nice to meet you.
- Ah.' Ryu Sanada.
I'm not great at memorizing
peoples' names. So sorry.
Ever since Kazehaya starting sitting next
to me... everything in my life... has changed
- so much.
- Kuronuma.
We've been having a tough timing coming
up with a name for the dog. You think... you
could name him?
- Please help me out?
- U-' Um, I...
Pedro Martínez.
Pedro Martínez. Yeah.
Pin?!
Pin? You're just the assistant
class teacher. Why are you here?
- Hm?
- Something happen to Zen?
- Isn't this his class?
- Seems like Zen has to
handle a couple issues at home.
So I'll be here, acting as his pinch
hitter for a little while! Don't worry~
I'll hit a grand slam!
- Issues at home? Is it because of Sadako?
- He did dump that work on her over break.
Pedro Martínez... Maru for short!
It's perfect!
That reminds me, Zen said something...
- Kuronuma.
- Yes.
Did ya see that?! ~
Aren't I just amazing?!
Seriously?
- That man's full of himself.
- but if Pin turns out to be okay, then
- it might be good for Sadako's reputation.
- Ah, that's true!
I see.
What was Mr. Pin doing? That was strange.
Kuronuma.
- I-It's hot today, huh?
- Yeah...
- What was that?
- I dunno. A comedy sketch, maybe?
What's happening?
This is different than it was with
Mr. Pin. My heart's beating way faster.
Yup! So, me and Ryu have been friends
ever since we were little kids. And we met
Kazehaya in middle school.
Chizu and I met later on, in high school
and we became friends because our seats
were next to each other.
That's wonderful! How was Kazehaya in
middle school, or has he been Mr. Prince
Charming forever?
Oh! ' Foreeeeeeeever! He's always been
just ' like that. -Never able to ignore
any of the outcasts in class, and always
the boys' leader, making him super popular
with the girls. -He was a nice
person even back in middle school!
So yeah, all the girls would be fighting
over him all the time. But after a while,
they realized Kazehaya hates all the
drama and stuff, so they ended up coming
together to make a compromise...
The "Kazehaya Belongs to Everyone"
Agreement. Everybody's Kazehaya.
You serious?! That's so stupid!
Incredible!
He's so powerful he can grab hold of
everyone's hearts and move them enough to
turn their feelings into actions!
Kazehaya, you sure are something else!
That's why so many of the girls who
went to our middle school decided to apply
- here.
- For example, that one?
Oh yeah. Exactly!
Even girls from different classes come
to see him. He has quite the reputation...
Hey, listen up! I need someone to
stay after school to make the roll book.
Isn't that supposed to be your job, Pin?!
Don't dump your dirty work on
us! Zen would do it himself.
Right! I'll do you the
honor of choosing then.
Everyone hates this. I'll do it.
That's boring, but fine.
Then I'll do it too. If we both do
it, it'll get done faster ' y'know!
I mean, if Kazehaya's
going to do it, then I guess...
I'm in too. ' Sure.
Suddenly, it's a popular job. Um, well,
i-i-if everyone else wants to do it that
- much then...
- Kuronuma.
You said you'd do it,
so you'll do it, right?
Right.
- It slipped right out of my mouth.
- What the heck did I just witness? That
was like a scene straight out of a dating
sim.
Kazehaya! See me in the faculty office!
That's all!
All rise.
Bow!
CLASS 1-D
ROLL BOOK
Then I'll do it too.
That made me so happy.
SHOTA KAZEHAYA
Hold on. Bathroom. BRB.
Kazehaya.
Pin went to the bathroom... so, I escaped.
- I'll help you.
- Oh, Th-Thank ' you.
Thank you... for everything.
What you did today helped me more than you
know, Kazehaya. I had such an amazing day
and it's because of you.
I didn't really do anything special
though. And it's not just me. ' I wouldn't
be surprised if ' everyone
wanted a chance to talk to you.
- Can I?
- S-Sure.
Mind if I write the rest of this?
Thank...
SAWAKO KURONUMA
1-D, Shota Kazehaya! Report to the
faculty office immediately! -If you don't
come within one minute, I'll expose your
embarrassing past to the whole school, all
of it! That's all! -Sorry, Kuronuma!
- I gotta go!
- Th- Thanks for the help!
Sorry, it's just...
- Kazehaya was in here, so...
- Those two are Hirano and Endo.
...they might be waiting... for
a chance to just talk to you.
Um...
Do you... want to sit down and chat?... Just
for a little bit. -I'll set up a place for
us right away. -Th-that's okay!
Again...
- I went and messed it up again.
- It's okay don't worry about it!
Yeah, we can do it ourselves.
Um, you aren't mad at us... are you?
- Thought so.
- It's just, Sada...
Kuronuma... you always have
this angry look going on so...
We just thought you
preferred being on your own.
But we overheard you with Yoshida and
Yano saying how happy you were to get to
- talk with them.
- Plus, lately, you've been greeting us
all the time. We wanted to know why so we
came by to check on you.
And Kazehaya said...
You don't have to stand
out in the hall. Go inside.
- Please let us help.
- You always end up doing these
random duties all by yourself.
- Why are you crying?
- They're... tears of joy.
- No way, you're actually a softie?
- Th-Thank you so much.
By the way... what did people call
you before the Sadako nickname?
The name I liked most
was zashiki-warashi.
- Uh, you were happy with that?
- Oh! you were so scary playing the
- ghost role at the test-of-courage!
- Mhm Mhm! I thought
you were the real thing! Right?
Ever since Kazehaya reached out and
gave me these chances... Little by little...
everything around me is
beginning to change for the better.
- You done already?
- Uh, yeah. Hirano and Endo came
by. They helped me out a ton.
Seriously? That's good to hear!
Th- Thanks so much.
Because of Kazehaya,' I can
feel myself starting to change.
I never been able to take action like
this. It's like you've given me power.
Haven't you noticed?
With Yano and Yoshida, Hirano and Endo
too. Everyone's moved by the effort you
put in, Kuronuma.
Don't you see?]
You've given power to me too...
and I want you to know that.
I'm doing for him... what he does for me?
I never could've imagined that.
But... if that really is the case...
that would make me so incredibly happy.
Nice going, Sadako!
- With the Hirano and Endo thing.
- I heard that they both helped you out.
They did~ and it's all
thanks to the two of you!
Since you've been talking to me. Because
of that... I think... Hirano and Endo felt a
lot more comfortable talking to me too.
So, thank you.
You idiot!
Translation: she wants you to know it's
because you did your best. She's right
about that, Sadako.
- That win's completely yours.
- I have no words... I still can't believe
how truly blessed I am to be able to talk
to such kind people...
- Oh yeah, by the way... what's that book?
- Uh, this? Ghost stories.
- Ghost stories?!
- I figured if I had this, I might be
able to live up to everyone's
expectations.
Sadako's story time?
Actually, I'm interested!
You're so dang positiiiiiive!
I guess it's either that or her
brain's just wired differently.
Uh, ~ so your midterms
will be covered up to here.
- This is bad!
- Seriously?!
Wha...
- And what are you doing, Kazehaya?!
- I was... Killing a bug?!
It was meant for Yano! I finally got my
very first mission and I butchered it...
TO KURONUMA, I MEANT
Ku-ro-nu-ma.
ONCE I GET HOME,
I'LL WALK MARU,
SO IF YOU'RE FREE,
COME SEE MARU.
RIVERBED WE PICKED HIM UP.
KAZE
I'LL GO.
My handwriting... got so shaky.
Once I drop these handouts off at the
faculty office, I'll go home, change
clothes and...
I'm getting too carried away.
I've gotta pull myself together.
Here.
Oh! Uh. Thanks.
No prob.
She looks like a French bisque doll. This
must be the luckiest time of my life right
now!
Wait! Maru!
Aww It's really him!
Come here!
Maru!
Wait~ that's what you wanted?
Yes! My treats tactic worked!
Hey! He likes it!
And now he's talking to me!
What kinda things do
you usually do, Kuronuma?
Oh... I study mostly.
I don't mean before
tests. In your free time.
I study... mostly?
Woah! And here I am, flying out the
door and barely making it in time!
Um, I guess there's something else?
Sometimes I imagine
things, and that's fun--
Oh, what do you mean by "imagine things"?
I make these scenarios. For example~ I
imagine the person sitting next to me in
class has a problem
they don't understand.
I ask them what part they got stuck on.
And then I try to think of how I can
explain it in the simplest way. Before I
knew it, studying like that
unintentionally became a habit for me.
By the way, I'm just curious,
did you tell anyone about Maru?
Mm-mm. gotcha.
In other words. Only the two of us know
about you finding him and me adopting him,
huh?
Right, then I'm not
gonna tell anyone else.
That smile...
All of his smiles... Even though so many
other people get to see them, for this
moment at least... I get them all to myself.
They give me hope that tomorrow... will be
another wonderful day.
Kuronuma.
Can you teach me this part?
I'm the person sitting next to you.
They used "what" here, but I don't
really understand. Could you explain it?
- Hm?
- Oh, in this context, the "what"
- is called a relative pronoun and...
- Hm?
Wait~ are you guys
actually studying over here?
So, that means it connects the dependent
clause here with an independent clause.
This one... to this.
- Oh! I see! Makes sense.
- Ah...
- What?
- Are they all getting tutored by Sadako?
Hang on, I think I get it!
So then, if you were to
connect this one here with this one...
I did it! I figured it out this time!
I- I can't believe she
helped Yoshida solve a problem.
You know, you're really
good at teaching. For real.
What?
- Would you mind if we joined you guys?
- Please teach us, we're so lost.
- That's why... this is the same formula...
- Oh, yeah, you're right!
I couldn't get it no
matter how many times I tried.
- Me too!
- Here, if you do this...
- Even I could understand!
- Wow, you make it so easy!
You should get up front
and use the chalkboard.]
Thank you, Sadako!
- Please tutor us again, Miss Kuronuma!
- Thank you!
I helped! I finally did
something that really helped!
You sure do move to the
beat of your own drum, Sadako.
She...
She- she smi-
Wait, what?
Woah did you guys just see that?
K-Kazehaya.
- Well uh, today I--
- I'm happy for you! ' Just like our talk.
Everyone came over like
you've always wanted.
Of course that made me really happy.
But my scenario from yesterday had
already become a reality the moment that
you asked me to teach you. So, I know
you might be tired of hearing this, but I
still wanted to say...
Thank you.
Hey, Kazehaya!
- Oh, ' is he talking with someone?
- Let's head out.
Sorry, I'm a real selfish guy.
I thought I was the only one
who knew ~ about ~ that smile.
So, let me just have this one to myself.
This one's all mine.
Man, that is the first time
I've seen Sadako smile like that!
When you see her make a face like that,
she actually seems pretty normal, huh?
What? Really? ~ Yoshida... she's that
one girl with the narrow eyes, right?
Uh-huh! I heard she was a
delinquent and even went to juvie before.
Yeah! And the Yano girl too.
Apparently she's a total nympho!
Someone said she went through a
hundred guys just in middle school!
No way, girl, that's insane!
Hmmm? Oh, really now?
- And? Who exactly said that?
- Oh, uh...
Who, C'mon, spill it.
E-Everyone's been say--
Don't give me that. I'm asking
you where this bullcrap started!
- What's the source?
- Sa... Sadako
Misunderstood words.
Feelings that won't reach.
Next time: ~ "Rumors"